Personal Details:

Name: Sean Lee Jin Xiang

Nationality: Malaysian

Current Residence: Australia

Career Objective:

To research and work with an innovative company or research institution to gain experience in creating real time designs using software development and hardware and to use and enhance not only software engineering skills, but creativity, team skills and leadership through such experience.

Interests:

Academic:

- Web Design
- Software Development
- Graphics and Animation
- User Interface Development

Non-Academic:

- Travelling
- Sports
- Fishing
- Music

Work Experience:

2006-2008:	Thai Hutt Restaurant Job Title: Manager Responsibilities: Setting up shifts for the waiters and ensuring the waiters do their jobs efficiently and effectively. Managing the wages and ensuring the till is not short at the end of the day. This has taught me how to manage people and to keep calm under pressure.
2004-2006	Upamanis sdn. bhd.(Domestic Helper Agency) Job Title: Office Assistant Responsibilities: Making sure the correct documents gets sent to the correct customers and to deliver important documents such as immigration reports and bank drafts myself. What i have gained in this experience is to organize myself and my surroundings to create a easy and effective work environment.
2003-2004	Penang Little Restaurant. Job Title: Waiter Responsibilities: Attract people to become customers at the restaurant and maintaining top customer service. This was very helpful in developing my communications skills

Education:

2006-2008:	Diploma in Web Development At Technical And Further Education (TAFE) NSW. Currently Studying.
1998 - 2003:	Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia(SAM) (Equivalent to year 11,12) At Sekolah Menengah Sri Kuala Lumpur

Skill List:

Technical Skills

Web development:

Capable of developing interactive web pages using JavaScript, HTML, PHP, XML, CSS. Experienced in using Microsoft FrontPage, Macromedia Fireworks, Macromedia Flash, Macromedia Dreamworks, Adobe Photoshop and Paint Shop Pro. Database:

Experienced in building relational database using xampp which includes a combination of apache and mysql.

PC:

Have gained good experience in the use of MSWord, PowerPoint and other PC tools.

Platform:

Windows and MAC.

Leadership/Team Skills:

Coordinated with other members in the group of various sizes during all the group projects in the College, worked as a team leader in some of them.

Successfully delegated responsibility to group members for the completion of the projects undertaken.

Language Skills:

Fluent in English, Chinese(Cantonese, Mandrin) and Bahasa Melayu.

Referees:

Mark Praba is a fellow co-worker of Thai Hutt Restaurant and will vouch that I am easy to work with and a great asset to any organization. His contact number is 0406518992.

Susan See is the business owner of the Domestic Agency I worked for and is able to give you more information about me as a person and a co-worker. Her contact number is 0423631177.